Contact

katiebelleho@ucla.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/katiebho (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Excel

Teamwork

User Experience (UX)

Languages

Chinese Mandarin (Native or Bilingual)

Chinese Cantonese (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Design Thinking

Human-Computer Interaction

Business Analytics: Data Insights

Katie Ho

Product Designer at Trove

San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

I am a curious and motivated problem-solver with a passion for discovering user needs and translating them into design strategies. I have a propensity to learn quickly and the agility to wear multiple hats to drive results. My experiences in the eCommerce and Accounting industries gave me a diverse foundation of skills to design innovative solutions for complex problems.

Experience

Trove
Product Designer
February 2021 - Present (4 months)
San Francisco Bay Area

Omou Learning Product Designer August 2019 - Present (1 year 10 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

I worked with products, developers, and other designers to build a tutoring management platform for small to mid-sized tutoring centers to manage their daily operations.

• Conducted user research, created user flows, and designed wireframes & prototypes in all levels of fidelity for key features

Walmart eCommerce
Category Management Specialist
May 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 5 months)
San Francisco Bay Area

I managed and grew a multi-million product category by 55% with a vision to improve user experience on walmart.com.

 Drove customer-centric business strategies in assortment expansion and site UX

- Analyzed large datasets from various analytics tools to gain better insights into customer behavior
- Initiated and led several cross-functional team projects to optimize site experience and increase conversion

PwC

Tax Experienced Associate, Digital Transformation October 2017 - May 2019 (1 year 8 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

I drove process transformation initiatives across various tax teams using customized in-house digital solutions.

- Conducted interviews and brainstorming workshops with teams to identify pain points and inefficiencies in current tax reporting
- Automated complex tax processes by breaking them down into step-by-step flows
- Created Tableau dashboards to track team progress and visualize efficiency of digital tools.

UCLA Anderson School of Management Marketing Research Assistant September 2014 - June 2017 (2 years 10 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

- Analyzed research findings relating to branding, consumer identity, and formation of brand stigmatization
- Studied cultural differences in the US and Chinese consumer markets and their effects on consumers' receptiveness to marketing techniques and international market-entry strategies

PwC

Tax Reporting Strategy Intern June 2016 - August 2016 (3 months) Greater Los Angeles Area

Marcum LLP
Tax Intern
February 2016 - April 2016 (3 months)

Education

University of California, Los Angeles

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Double Majors in Business Economics and Psychology,

Minor in Accounting · (2013 - 2017)